sorry
frisbee Chandler rules Joey Garber Greg
get in the house get the house
how we doing today I'm doing we got a
call down there at the department some
aircraft taking off from our Reno
airport's been receiving some fire some
bullet rounds
what airline was it doesn't really
matter
Frisby honestly I don't shoot it airline
alien aircraft you only shoot at alien
aircraft what I think is there alien
aircraft et stuff uh-huh how would you
distinguish that from regular aircraft
it's got aliens in it what if you start
with alien spirits aircraft
what if alien they were just you know
doing a little uh drive-by and you start
taking shots at them and suddenly holy
we just took a first shot at alien
spacecraft it's good question what's
your name
Travis Travis Travis that's a good
question thank you
how lucky look I like you're lost out
thanks a lot but a nice house got a good
good wife second cousin doing man hi I'm
good thanks if we were to look say for
example in that bunker that covered with
the tarp right before we came over I
ain't been over there and so long I have
knotty I haven't been over there and you
never make it through this corner of the
yard
well we keep ours this is not yours oh
honey that shut up I'm sorry
Brisby yeah I got this at a yard sale
what so you shouldn't have these kids
right there that and the oranges all
right so just Parker huh get to it
all right put the hand in here we go he
didn't beat him bleed let him bleed
that was pretty cool can I do it next
circle Heth
you